

@

kumarsandeep.k7259@gmail .com



+91 9110859225



Bangalore India



https://www.linkedin.com/in /sandeep-kumar-k

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Engineering: Electronics And Communication Engineering MVJ COLLEGE OF ENGINEERING, Bangalore, June 2023

• 8 CGPA

Diploma: Electronics And Communication Engineering GOVERNMENT

POLYTECHNIC, Chintamani, October 2020

• 79%

SSLC

SFS HIGH SCHOOL, Chintamani, April 2017

• 91.84%

LANGUAGES

English

Bilingual or Proficient (C2)

Kannada

Bilingual or Proficient (C2)

Telugu

Advanced (C1)

Hindi

Intermediate (B1)

SANDEEP KUMAR K

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Honors in Electronics and Communication Engineering with demonstrate experience on Embedded system, IoT and implementing end-to-end solutions for problem solving. To seek and maintain full-time position that offers professional challenges utilizing interpersonal skills and technical skills, excellent time management and problem-solving skills.

SKILLS

- · Embedded System
- · IoT
- Electronics
- · C, C++

- · Python
- · Aspice Model
- Good Communication Skill
- · MS office

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

February 2023 - June 2023

Pi Square Technologies India Pvt Ltd - Internship - Embedded Testing and IoT, Bangalore

September 2022 - October 2022

AiRobosoft - Internship - Machine Learning and Internship

May 2022 - July 2022

Skill Vertex - Internship - IoT & Robotics

CERTIFICATIONS

Industrial Automation Training Program on Embedded Systems & Robotics - Aqmenz Automation Pvt Ltd

IoT and Robotics - Skill Vertex

Cyber Security Professional Basics - CSC Academy

Python - Udemy

C++ - Great Learning

C-Udemy

Cybersecurity Essentials - Cisco Nasscom Futureskills

Indian Institute of Banking and Finance

PROJECTS

- Smart Gardener (Final Year Project) Its a smart Lawn grass cutter, it is a proposed solution to automate the lawn maintenance process using an intelligent lawn cutter with advanced sensing capabilities.
- Alcohol and Drowsiness Detection (Pi Square Technologies) The model is to detect the alcohol and drowsiness of the driver, if the alcohol or drowsiness reaches above the limited range, then the buzzer turns on and at certain time the car needs to turn off.
- Spam Mail Prediction using Machine learning (AiRobosoft) The project is to predict the mail whether it is spam mail or ham mail using AI/ML.
- Microver_IoTA- It is an IoT project, to provide the server and firmware for IoT user.
- · Smart Home Automation Using IoT
- · Pick and Place Robot
- · Hand controlled car